question_data = ({"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Half-Life 2 runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Super Mario 3D World, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
                     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the game Subnautica, a Spadefish will attack you.",
                  "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
                     "correct_answer": "True",
                     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question":
                         "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named Timmy and Jimmy.",
                     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
                  "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question":
                         "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
                     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Undertale, the main character of the game is Sans.",
                  "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question": "Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
                     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The game Pocket Morty has a Morty called Pocket Mortys Morty?",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question": "The game Jetpack Joyride was created by Redbrick Studios.",
                     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
                  "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
                     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                     "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.",
                     "correct_answer": "False",
                     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]})

""" https://opentdb.com/api_config.php ....Try this link to generate new questions for the quiz game."""
